(Leonard:)But the mission wouldn't be
for at least a year.
(Leonard:)Isn't that enough time to get
your blood pressure under--
(Howard:)My blood pressure's too high, okay?
Drop it.
(Penny:)You know, my aunt changed her diet,
and in a few months, she--
(Howard:)Went to space? I don't think so.
Now, pass the soy sauce.
(Howard:)Not the green one, the red one.
(Penny:)Sheldon, Amy,
will you please come join us?
(Bernadette:)It's fun up here.
(Leonard:)So why are you trying to ruin it?
(Sheldon:)No, thanks. We're fine.
(Sheldon:)I mean, if you people
want to eat at the table,
(Sheldon:)then that's what you should do.
(Sheldon:)I like eating down here
(Sheldon:)because this is how
we've always done things.
(Sheldon:)But if those days are gone,
they're gone.
(Sheldon:)It just makes me sad.
(Bernadette:)Now I feel bad.
(Leonard:)Don't anthropomorphize him,
he's got big eyes,
(Leonard:)but his feelings are not like ours.
(Bernadette:)No, It just seems silly
for us to sit in two groups.
Lt's not silly
if you think of that group
(Leonard:)as being led by a big, evil baby.
(Bernadette:)Look at Amy down there.
(Bernadette:)Should we go?
(Penny:)Let's go.
(Leonard:)Penny, this was your idea.
(Leonard:)You said that I should
stand up to him.
(Penny:)Forget it, Leonard.
(Penny:)It's over.
(Penny:)Fine.
(Amy:)Rajesh?
(Raj:)Screw that! I sat
on the floor for seven years.
I'm staying right here!
(Bernadette:)Come on, Raj,
it's not the same without you.
(Penny:)Fine.
(Raj:)But no more making fun
of how I say tings.
You mean "tings"
like "moo-stache"?
(Sheldon:)Well, isn't this nice.
(Sheldon:)Sometimes the baby wins.